{
    "id": "385de1b729434072b8e5f2f8ed4434aa",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Is anybody ............................. home?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ee7d56094cb6422989afb87d9b9233cc"
        },
        {
            "question": "I met him .............................. Tokyo.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bbdba727c01d4458906d56b4a5a4570e"
        },
        {
            "question": "They have a cottage ........................... the hills.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2bd3fe0fb04b46c78e66ccbe11794672"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is a picture ........................... page six.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c24c6270845d46b6b532b76240afb567"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is a library ......................... the corner of the street.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f13b941b5bf84dd19f49657a7ec77767"
        },
        {
            "question": "Their office is ................................. the first floor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "668f27507ca0498292eedc4548fa3883"
        },
        {
            "question": "Many a man has drowned ........................... the sea.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fabbb8ce7b3049cd897dcbaed26396b7"
        },
        {
            "question": "There were very few vegetarian dishes ............................ the menu.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4f7acfd2df29407ea86d9abaac8a8e8e"
        },
        {
            "question": "There was a cat sleeping ............................. the corner of the room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9eac612fc2004a93b488e011a7d82b7e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I met her ............................. a conference.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a692aa0045f94a0a88eaed24f634f50f"
        },
        {
            "question": "There were books lying ............................. the floor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4e9e42dad6d54500a465bbd52b0af9a7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is that boy .............................. the front row?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "acf4ccd305184218af3e54c982335a5c"
        }
    ]
}